Jensen, Vernon Collection of International Longshoremen's Association's and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Materials 5487
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-120 (1968: June 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-120 (1968: June 24)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-121 (1968: June 25)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-122 (1968: June 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-123 (1968: June 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-124 (1968: June 28)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  July
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-125 (1968: July 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-126 (1968: July 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-127 (1968: July 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-128 (1968: July 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-129 (1968: July 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-130 (1968: July 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-131 (1968: July 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-132 (1968: July 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-133 (1968: July 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-134 (1968: July 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-135 (1968: July 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-136 (1968: July 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-137 (1968: July 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-138 (1968: July 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-139 (1968: July 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-140 (1968: July 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-141 (1968: July 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-142 (1968: July 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-143 (1968: July 26)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-144 (1968: July 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-145 (1968: July 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.68-146 (1968: July 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-147 (1968: Aug. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-148 (1968: Aug. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-149 (1968: Aug. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-150 (1968: Aug. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-151 (1968: Aug. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-152 (1968: Aug. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-153 (1968: Aug. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-154 (1968: Aug. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-155 (1968: Aug. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-156 (1968: Aug. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-157 (1968: Aug. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-158 (1968: Aug. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-159 (1968: Aug. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-160 (1968: Aug. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-161 (1968: Aug. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-162 (1968: Aug. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-163 (1968: Aug. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-164 (1968: Aug. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-165 (1968: Aug. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-166 (1968: Aug. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-167 (1968: Aug. 29)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Notes: no.68-168 (1968: Aug. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-169 (1968: Sep. 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-170 (1968: Sep. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-171 (1968: Sep. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-172 (1968: Sep. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-173 (1968: Sep. 9)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-174 (1968: Sep. 10)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-175 (1968: Sep. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-176 (1968: Sep. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-177 (1968: Sep. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-178 (1968: Sep. 16)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-179 (1968: Sep. 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-180 (1968: Sep. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-181 (1968: Sep. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-181 (1968: Sep. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-182 (1968: Sep. 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-183 (1968: Sep. 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-184 (1968: Sep. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-185 (1968: Sep. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-186 (1968: Sep. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.68-187 (1968: Sep. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-188 (1968: Oct. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-189 (1968: Oct. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-190 (1968: Oct. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-191 (1968: Oct. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-192 (1968: Oct. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-193 (1968: Oct. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-194 (1968: Oct. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-195 (1968: Oct. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-196 (1968: Oct. 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-197 (1968: Oct. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-198 (1968: Oct. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-199 (1968: Oct. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-200 (1968: Oct. 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-201 (1968: Oct. 18)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-202 (1968: Oct. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-203 (1968: Oct. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-204 (1968: Oct. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-205 (1968: Oct. 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-206 (1968: Oct. 25)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-207 (1968: Oct. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-208 (1968: Oct. 29)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-209 (1968: Oct. 30)
  - Item 23: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Notes: no.68-210 (1968: Oct. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-211 (1968: Nov. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-212 (1968: Nov. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-213 (1968: Nov. 6)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-214 (1968: Nov. 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-216 (1968: Nov. 12)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-217 (1968: Nov. 13)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-218 (1968: Nov. 14)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-219 (1968: Nov. 15)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-220 (1968: Nov. 18)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-221 (1968: Nov. 19)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-222 (1968: Nov. 20)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-223 (1968: Nov. 21)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-224 (1968: Nov. 22)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-225 (1968: Nov. 25)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-226 (1968: Nov. 26)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-227 (1968: Nov. 27)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Notes: no.68-228 (1968: Nov. 29)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-229 (1968: Dec. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-230 (1968: Dec. 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-231 (1968: Dec. 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-232 (1968: Dec. 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-233 (1968: Dec. 6)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-234 (1968: Dec. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-235 (1968: Dec. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-236 (1968: Dec. 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-237 (1968: Dec. 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-238 (1968: Dec. 13)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-239 (1968: Dec. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-240 (1968: Dec. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-241 (1968: Dec. 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-242 (1968: Dec. 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-243 (1968: Dec. 20)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-244 (1968: Dec. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-245 (1968: Dec. 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-246 (1968: Dec. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Notes: no.68-247 (1968: Dec. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-1 (1969: Jan. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-2 (1969: Jan. 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-3 (1969: Jan. 6)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-4 (1969: Jan. 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-5 (1969: Jan. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-6 (1969: Jan. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-7 (1969: Jan. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-8 (1969: Jan. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-9 (1969: Jan. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-10 (1969: Jan. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-11 (1969: Jan. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-12 (1969: Jan. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-13 (1969: Jan. 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-14 (1969: Jan. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-15 (1969: Jan. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-16 (1969: Jan. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-17 (1969: Jan. 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-18 (1969: Jan. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-19 (1969: Jan. 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-20 (1969: Jan. 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-21 (1969: Jan. 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Notes: no.69-22 (1969: Jan. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-23 (1969: Feb. 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-24 (1969: Feb. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-25 (1969: Feb. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-26 (1969: Feb. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-27 (1969: Feb. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-28 (1969: Feb. 11)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-29 (1969: Feb. 13)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-30 (1969: Feb. 14)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-31 (1969: Feb. 17)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-32 (1969: Feb. 18)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-33 (1969: Feb. 19)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-34 (1969: Feb. 20)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-35 (1969: Feb. 21)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-36 (1969: Feb. 24)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-37 (1969: Feb. 25)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-38 (1969: Feb. 26)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-39 (1969: Feb. 27)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Notes: no.69-40 (1969: Feb. 28)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-41 (1969: Mar. 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-42 (1969: Mar. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-43 (1969: Mar. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-44 (1969: Mar. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-45 (1969: Mar. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-46 (1969: Mar. 10)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-47 (1969: Mar. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-48 (1969: Mar. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-49 (1969: Mar. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-50 (1969: Mar. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-51 (1969: Mar. 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-52 (1969: Mar. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-53 (1969: Mar. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-54 (1969: Mar. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-55 (1969: Mar. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-56 (1969: Mar. 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-57 (1969: Mar. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-58 (1969: Mar. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-59 (1969: Mar. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-60 (1969: Mar. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Notes: no.69-61 (1969: Mar. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-62 (1969: Apr. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-63 (1969: Apr. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-64 (1969: Apr. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-65 (1969: Apr. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-66 (1969: Apr. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-67 (1969: Apr. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-68 (1969: Apr. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-69 (1969: Apr. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-70 (1969: Apr. 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-71 (1969: Apr. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-72 (1969: Apr. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-73 (1969: Apr. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-74 (1969: Apr. 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-75 (1969: Apr. 18)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-76 (1969: Apr. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-77 (1969: Apr. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-78 (1969: Apr. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-79 (1969: Apr. 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-80 (1969: Apr. 25)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-81 (1969: Apr. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Notes: no.69-82 (1969: Apr. 29)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-84 (1969: May 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-85 (1969: May 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-86 (1969: May 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-87 (1969: May 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-88 (1969: May 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-89 (1969: May 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-90 (1969: May 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-91 (1969: May 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-92 (1969: May 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-93 (1969: May 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-94 (1969: May 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-95 (1969: May 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-96 (1969: May 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-97 (1969: May 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-98 (1969: May 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-99 (1969: May 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-100 (1969: May 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-101 (1969: May 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-102 (1969: May 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-103 (1969: May 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Notes: no.69-104 (1969: May 29)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-105 (1969: June 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-106 (1969: June 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-107 (1969: June 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-108 (1969: June 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-109 (1969: June 6)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-110 (1969: June 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-111 (1969: June 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-112 (1969: June 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-113 (1969: June 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-114 (1969: June 13)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-115 (1969: June 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-116 (1969: June 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-117 (1969: June 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-118 (1969: June 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Notes: no.69-119 (1969: June 20)